- Volume 135: Witchcraft Papers Index 1692-1759
  - Examination of Mary Black, Apr 22, 1692, 20
    Page 18
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth v. Mary Witheridge, May 18, 1692, 21
    Page 19
  - Buckly, Sarah Examination, May 18, 1692, 22
    Page 20
  - Putnam, Ann v. Sarah Buckly, May 18, 1692, 23
    Page 21
  - Arnold, John Account of expenses March - May, 1692, 24
    Page 22
  - Newton, Thos Letter, May 31, 1692, 25
    Page 23
  - Good, Sarah & others Warrant (copy), May 31, 1692, 25
  - Warren, Mary Shelden Susannah & others v. Job Tuckey, June 4, 1692, 26
    Page 24
  - Lauder, John Stacy, John v. Job Tuckey, June 4, 1692, 27
    Page 25
  - Examination of Job Tucky, June 7, 1692, 28
    Page 26
  - Hubbard, William Petition for Sarah Buckly, June 20, 1692, 29
    Page 27
  - Swan, Timothy v. Richard Carrier, June, 1692, 30
    Page 28
  - Walcott, Mary v. Candy, July 2, 1692, 31
    Page 29
  - Putnam, Ann v. Candy, July 2, 1692, 31/2
    Page 30
  - Warren, Mary v. Job Tookey June 7, 1692, 32
    Page 31
  - Johnson, Eliz., Jr Confession, Aug. 11, 1692, 33
    Page 32
  - Hutchinson, Benjamin Deposition v. Sarah Buckly & Mary Witheridge Sept 15, 1692, 35
    Page 33
  - Sprague, Martha v. Sarah Bridges, Aug. 25, 1692, 36
    Page 34
  - Martin, Abigail v. William Barker, August, 37
    Page 35
  - Indictment of William Barker, 38
    Page 36
  - Barker, William Confession, Sept 5, 1692 duplicate, 39
    Page 37
  - Bridges, Sarah Indictment of Sarah Bridges, 40
    Page 38
  - Johnson, Stephen Indictment of Stephen Johnson, 41
    Page 39
  - Sprague, Martha Mary Lacey, Rose Foster v. Stephen Johnson, Sept. 1, 1692, 42
    Page 40
  - Walcott, Mary v. Sarah Buckly Sept. 14, 1692, 43
    Page 41
  - Putnam, Ann Deposition v. Sarah Buckly, Sept. 15, 1692, 44
    Page 42
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth Sarah Buckly, Sept. 14, 1692, 45
    Page 43
  - Marsten, Mary Examination & Confession, Sept. 15, 1692, 47
    Page 44
  - Phelps, Sarah Warren, Mary v. Abigail Faulkner Sept 17, 1692, 48
    Page 45
  - Foster, Rose Sprague, Martha v. Abigail Faulkner Sept 17, 1692 Abigail Faulkner Verdict & sentence, Sept. 17, 1692, 49
    Page 46
  - Walcott, Mary v. Abigail Faulkner, Sept. 17, 1692, 50
    Page 47
  - v. Abigail Faulkner, Sept. 17 1692 duplicate. image, 50
  - Indictment of Edward Farrington Duplicate image, 51
    Page 48
  - Warren, Mary v. Edward Farrington Sept 7, 1692, 52
    Page 49
  - Foster, Rose v. Hannah Tyler Sept 7, 1692, 53
    Page 50
  - Foster, Rose v. Abigail Barker Sept 8, 1692, 54
    Page 51
  - Wright, Walter Faulkner Francis Bond for John Sawdy, Oct. 6, 1692, 55
    Page 52
  - Osgood, John, Sr Dane, Nathaniel, Sr Bond for Dorothy & Abigail Faulkner, Oct. 6, 1692, 56
    Page 53
  - Faulkner, Francis & others Bond for Mary Lacy, Jr., Oct. 6, 1692, 57
    Page 54
  - Wright, Walter & others Bond for Stephen & Abigail Johnson & Sarah Carrier, Oct 6, 1692, 58
    Page 55
  - Petition for John Osgood, John Fry, John Marston & others Oct 12, 1692, 59
    Page 56
  - Bridges, John Osgood, John Bond for Mary Bridges, Oct. 15, 1692, 60
    Page 57
  - Petition of ministers of Andover, Oct 18, 1692, 61
    Page 59
  - Hart, Thomas Petition for Elizabeth Hart Oct 19, 1692, 62
    Page 60
  - Rist, Nicholas Petition for Sarah Rist, Oct. 19, 1692, 63
    Page 61
  - Barrett, Thomas Petition for Martha Sparks Nov 1, 1692, 64
    Page 62
  - Parker, John & Joseph Petition for Mary Parker, 65
    Page 63
  - Osgood, John Petition for accused Dec 6, 1692, 66
    Page 64
  - BLANK
    Page
  - Herrick, George Compensation Dec 8, 1692, 67
    Page 66
  - Legislative bill for more specificity in execution of laws against witchcraft, 68
    Page 67
  - BLANK
  - Niccolls, John Town, Joseph Bond for William Hobbs, Dec14, 1692, 70
    Page 69
  - Prince, Thomas Tan, Richard Bond for Margaret Prince, Dec 15, 1692, 71
    Page 70
  - Green, Peter Sanders, James Bond for Mary Green, Dec 16, 1692, 72
    Page 71
  - Frie, John Osgood, John Eunice Frie, Dec 20, 1692 Duplicate, 73
    Page 72
  - Osgood, John Frie, John Bond for Mary Osgood, Dec 20, 1692, 74
    Page 73
  - Hutchens, Samuel Kingsbury, Joseph Bond for Frances Hutchens, Dec 29, 1692, 75
    Page 74
  - Fox, Rebecca Petition for Rebecca Jacobs, 76
    Page 75
  - Warrant for jurors -- Lynn, Dec 25, 1692, 77
    Page 76
  - Warrant for jurors -- Ipswich, Dec 23, 1692, 79
    Page 77
  - Warrant for jurors -- Salem, Dec 23, 1692, 81
    Page 78
  - Warrant for jurors -- Gloucester, Dec 23, 1692, 83
    Page 79
  - Warrant for jurors -- Marblehead, Dec 23, 1692, 84
    Page 80
  - Warrant for jurors -- Topsfield, Dec 23, 1692, 85(86?)
    Page 81
  - Warrant for jurors -- Beverly, Dec 20, 1692, 88
    Page 82
  - Warrant for jurors -- Haverhill, Dec 23, 1692, 90
    Page 83
  - Warrant for jurors -- Andover, Dec 23, 1692, 92
    Page 84
  - Warrant for jurors -- Newbury, Dec 23, 1692, 93
    Page 85
  - Return of jurors -- Rowly Dec 31, 1692, 95
    Page 86
  - Warrant for jurors -- Wenham, Dec 23, 1692, 96
    Page 87
  - Return of jurors -- Newbury, Dec 30, 1692, 97
    Page 88
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth v. Rebecca Jacobs, May 18, 1692, 98
    Page 89
  - Higginson, John Cheever, Samuel Petition for Mrs Buckly, Jan 2, 1692/3, 99
    Page 90
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth v. Margaret Jacobs, May 11, 1692, 100
    Page 91
  - Indictment of Mercy Wardwell, 101
    Page 92
  - Osgood, John Fry, James Bond for Eunice Fry, Jan 2, 1692/3, 102
    Page 93
  - Bridges, John Osgood, John Bond for Mary Bridges, Jan 2, 1692/3, 103
    Page 94
  - Faulkner, Francis Marble, Joseph Bond for Dorothy & Abigail Faulkner Jan 13, 1692 Duplicate images, 104
    Page 95
  - Barker, John Osgood, John Bond for William & Mary Barker Jan 13, 1692/3, 105
    Page 96
  - Osgood, John Wilson, Joseph Bond for Sarah Wilson, Jr & Sarah Wilson, Sr Jan 13, 1692, 106
    Page 97
  - Tyler, Hopestill Bridges, John Bond for Martha & Johanna Tyler Jan 13, 1692/3, 107
    Page 98
  - Cole, Abraham Bond for Sarah Cole Jan 14, 1692/3, 108
    Page 99
  - Procter, Elizabeth Petition to recover her husband's estate, June 10, 1696, 109
    Page 100
  - Phillips, Timothy Petition for compensation, Mar 18, 1696/7, 110
    Page 101
  - Phillips, Timothy Account of expenses Mar 22, 1696/7 Payment for expenses Dec 16, 1697, 111
    Page 102
  - Faulkner, Abigail Petition to clear condemnation as a witch June 13, 1700, 113
    Page 103
  - Examination of Abigail Faulkner (copy) Aug 11, 1692, 115 116 117
    Page 104 105
  - Phelps, Sarah Indictment of Abigail Faulkner (copy), 118
    Page 105a
  - Putnam, Ann v. Abigail Faulkner, Sept. 17, 1692, 119
    Page 106
  - Faulkner, Abigail Indictment of Abigail Faulkner, 120
    Page 107
  - Petition to clear records of accused, mar 2, 1702/3, 121 122
    Page 108
  - Faulkner, Mary & others Memorandum for Bill to acquit accused, 123
    Page 109
  - House of Rep. Order for Bill to prohibit future witchcraft prosecutions July 21, 1703, 124
  - Memorial to clear reputations of accused, July 16, 1703, 124
    Page 110
  - Memorial to clear reputations of accused, May 25, 1709, 125
    Page 111
  - Memorial to clear reputations of accused, May 25, 1709, 126
    Page 112
  - English, Philip Petition for restitution, 1692, 127 128 128
    Page 113 113a 114
  - Esty, Isaac, Sr Petition for restitution for Mary Esty, Sept. 8, 1710, 130
    Page 115
  - How, Mary & Abigail Petition for restitution for Eliz. How, Sept. 9, 1710, 131
    Page 116
  - Bishop, Edward Petition for restitution for Bridget Bishop, Sept. 9, 1710, 132
    Page 117
  - Wildes, Ephraim Petition for restitution for Sarah Wild, Sept. 11, 1710, 133
    Page 118
  - King, John & Annus Petition for restitution for Dorcas Hoar, 134
    Page 119
  - True, Henry & Jane Petition for restitution for Mary Bradbury Sept. 11, 1710, 135
    Page 120
  - Burroughs, Charles Petition for restitution for George Burroughs, 136
    Page 121
  - Lacy, Lawrence Petition for restitution for Mary Lacy, 137
  - Barker, John Payment for jail fee Wm Barker, Mary Barker, 138 139
    Page 122
  - Prestion, Sarah Petition for restitution for sarah Bridges, 140
    Page 123
  - Wright (Wardwell), Mercy Petition for restitution for Mercy Wardwell, 141
  - Johnson, John Petition for restitution for Rebecca Johnson, 142
    Page 124
  - Marston, John Petition for restitution for Mary Marston, 143
  - Jacob, George, Jr. Petition for restitution for George Jacob, Sr, 144
  - Wilson, John Petition for restitution for wife Sarah & daughter Sarah, 145
    Page 126
  - Barker, Ebenezer Petition for restitution for Abigail Barker, 146
  - Dane, Nathaniel Petition for restitution for Deliverance Dane, 147
    Page 127
  - Barker, John Petition for restitution for Wm Barker, Jr., 149
  - Morey, Mary Petition for restitution for Sarah Morey, 150
    Page 128
  - Emes, Rebecca Petition for restitution for Rebecca Emes, Sept. 12, 1710, 151
    Page 129
  - Osgood, Samuel Petition for restitution for Mary Osgood, 1710, 152
    Page 130
  - Post, Mary Petition for restitution for imprisionment, Sept. 13, 1710, 153
  - Faulkner, Abigail Petition for restitution, Sept. 13, 1710, 154
    Page 131
  - Cole, Sarah Petition for restitution for imprisonment, Sept. 13, 1710, 155
    Page 132
  - Hobs, William Petition for restitution for imprisonment, sept. 13, 1710, 156
  - Johnson, Francis Petition for restitution for Eliz. Johnson, Jr, Sept. 13, 1710, 157
    Page 133
  - Lacy, Lawrence Petition for restitution for Mary Lacy, Sept. 13, 1710, 158
    Page 134
  - Foster, Abraham Petition for restitution for Anne Foster, Sept. 13, 1710, 159
    Page 135
  - Buckly, William Petition for restitution for Sarah Buckly & Mary Witherige, Sept. 13, 1710, 160
    Page 136
  - Moulton, John Petition for restitution for Marth & Giles Cory, Sept. 13, 1710, 161
    Page 137
  - Johnson, Francis Petition for restitution for Eliz. Johnson, Jr., Sept. 13, 1710, 162
    Page 138
  - Carrier, Thomas Petition for restitutiion for Martha Carrier, Sept. 13, 1710, 163
    Page 139
  - Wardwell, Samuel Petition for restitution for sarah & Samuel Wardwell, Sr., Sept. 13, 1710, 164
    Page 140
  - Nurse, Samuel Petition for restitution for Rebecca Nurse, Sept. 13, 1710, 165
    Page 141
  - Johnson, Francis Petition for restitution for Sarah Hawks, Sept. 14, 1710, 166
    Page 142
  - Town, Margaret Memorial for John Willard, Sept. 13, 1710, 167
    Page 143
  - Parker, John & Joseph Memorial for Mary Parker, Sept. 13, 1710, 168
    Page 144
  - Report of General Court on reversal of attainders of accused Oct. 26, 1711, 169
    Page 145
  - Green, Peter Peititon for restitution for his wife, 170
    Page 146
  - Expenses of General Court for reversal of attainders Oct. 30, 1711, 171
  - Newman, Thomas & others Memorial for George Burroughs, Mar. 28, 1750, 172
    Page 147